So Side Quest Slayer is for all my vision board girlies out there and at the beginning of
the year, we create a vision board of all of our hopes and dreams.
But then the months go on, life happens and we might not be closer to our dreams.
So introducing Side Quest Slayer, you choose a quest whether that's building a business,
learning a skill, becoming a content creator, and you can basically
post the journey towards achieving whatever goal.
Let's say you want to run a marathon, you can post pictures of you running outside
and maybe there's a beautiful sunset or maybe you see something along the way, maybe you
buy an outfit, you buy new shoes, you go to the gym, you basically document the journey.
So then when you're finally running that marathon, it's not just celebrating that final
moment, you celebrate all of the moments that lead up towards your goal.
So yeah, it's called Side Quest Slayer, it's in the app store and I hope you get it.